Go, go!
走，快走
Approaching.
靠近目标
I think we have touchdown.
我想这回应该是个真家伙
Little to the right
- 往右一点 - 好的，向右
Hello mum
你好啊，老妈
Now, push it in
好了，往里面捅
I can't
不行啊
What do you mean you can't? Pretend it's your dick, man.
不行个屁 就把它当成你的老二，往前推
You'll never get in if you did that.
那你就别想完事了
- Here, let me have a shot. - Give me a second,
- 我来试试 - 再等一会儿
- No, come on - My dick, man - Go
- 少来，让开，这是我的老二 - 给你
Fucker
操性
- Got that - Yeah
- 拿住了 - 嗯
Here we go
开场了
- Oh, look at that - Nice 155, huh? - Yeah
- 好正的T155啊(注：聚异丁烯丁二酰亚胺) - 是啊
It's going to do some fucking damage.
这玩意儿要是炸了，可了不得
Hey, Eldridge, looks like we're going to need a charge!
喂，艾缀奇，看来需要来一次引爆
I got that.
收到
Figured four blocks that'll give us about 20 pounds of bang total.
我估计用四盒就能产生20磅当量了
That blast is going to roast straight out there.
爆炸波会一直冲到那儿
The shell will probably kick out there, and most of the shrapnel
弹壳可能会飞到那个地方
is going to shoot straight up in a beautiful umbrella pattern.
其他零散的弹片会像天女散花一样
Yep
没错
We're gonna get some smaller pieces and shell fragments this way,
还有些碎弹片会飞向我们这边
but we'll be okay if we're behind the Humvee,
只要站在军用悍马后面应该没啥问题
- Bring the bot back, we'll load it up. - No problem.
- 把机器人叫回来，准备引爆 - 好的
Bot is moving.
机器人正在返回
Let me know what you got, Eldridge.
艾缀奇，报告情况
Good to go.
已经准备好了
All right, wagon's set up. Bot moves.
好，让小车上路
Uh-oh, we got goats, guys!
啊哦，半路杀出一帮山羊
Goats 12:00, Watch out,
注意，12点钟方向出现羊群
Load them little bastards up.
弹药上膛…
- Oh, shit, - Shit,
哦，该死
Oh, fuck!
他娘的
Wagon's having a bad day, boys.
小车倒了怎么推哟
- You build that? - No, the U.S. Army did,
- 是你造的？ - 不，是美国陆军造的
All right, looks like I'm going down there
好，看来得我去搞定
You don't like waiting around this beautiful neighborhood?
这么美丽的小区，不想再流连一会儿？
Oh, I love it.
哦，真喜欢这儿啊
So, if everything looks okay, when I get down there
如果一切顺利，我过去之后
I'm just going to set it up and bip it,
把那玩意儿设好，然后引爆
Give these people something to think about,
让这些家伙明白明白
Want them to know if they're gonna leave a bomb on the side of the road for us,
既然要在我们前进的路上放炸弹
we're just going to blow up their little fuckin' road,
我们只好把他们的路炸开
Sounds good
有理
Craving a burger; is that strange?
我想吃汉堡了，是不是有些怪？
- Not for you - No, okay
- 你这么说，不觉得奇怪 - 那好
Helmet on
戴上头盔
Happy trails
祝旅途愉快
Blaster One, can you read me?
我是拆弹1号，能听见么
Roger that, Blaster one. You're good to go.
收到，拆弹1号，你可以出发了
You're looking good, Blaster One.
拆弹1号，你看上去很棒
Nice and hot in here.
好是好，就是热
Roger that, 150 meters
收到，150米
Hi!
喂
- Where are you from? - Whoa, whoa, whoa!
- 你们从哪儿来？ - 且慢
Where are you from?
- 你们从哪儿来？从哪儿来的？ - 停下
California?
加利福尼亚？
- Hey, get out of here, man - Where?
- 走开，伙计 - 是哪儿呢？
Hey, this ain't no fuckin' meet and greet. Now get out of here.
没功夫和你闲聊，快走开！
Go!
走开
You making friends again, Sanborn?
又认识新朋友啦，桑伯恩？
All day long
整天都在认识
Twenty-five meters, Roger that You are now in the kill zone.
25米，收到，你已进入死亡区域
Thanks for reminding me.
谢谢提醒
That's what I'm here for, baby.
我就是干这个的
Okay-
好吧
The debts look good.
引爆装置没坏
Roger that.
收到
I'm laying on the charge.
现在放引爆器
Nice and sweet.
小心轻放
We're good to go.
一切就绪
I'm coming back.
现在返回
- Five meters out. - Five meters, Roger that.
- 已经走出5米 - 5米，收到
Hey, Sanborn
桑伯恩
- You know what this place needs? - I'm listening.
- 知道这儿缺什么嘛 - 说说看
Needs grass
缺草皮
We gonna start our grass business?
我们该在这儿卖草皮？
That's right, man.
没错，伙计
I'm going to sell the grass, you're going to cut it.
我来卖草皮，你去修草坪
It's going to be called ''Sanborn and Sons'',
公司名就叫“桑伯恩子弟”
We'll be rich.
我们会发财的
I like that, crabgrass, St. Augustine, man.
这点子我喜欢 马唐(杂草名)，钝叶草…
I'm a scholar on this shit,
这方面我是行家
How about this? You sell it, I fertilize it.
不如这样，你卖草，我种草
- 25 - 25 meters, Roger that
- 25 - 25米，收到
Sanborn!
桑伯恩！
Butcher shop, 2:00! dude has a phone!
2点钟方向有家肉店，老板拿着手机！
Why is Eldridge running?
艾缀奇为啥要跑？
- Make him put it down! - Put down the phone!
- 命令他放下手机！ - 放下手机！
Come on, guys, talk to me,
快点，伙计们，告诉我怎么了
Drop the phone! Drop your phone!
手机扔掉！手机扔掉！
Hey, burn him, Eldridge! Burn him!
开枪打他，艾缀奇，射他！
- Put down the cell phone! - Eldridge, burn him!
- 放下手机 - 艾缀奇，打他！
- Get out of the way, - Drop your phone!
- 让开 - 交出你的手机！
Make him put it down! Go get it!
命令他放下手机！ 去拿过来！
- Come on, Eldridge! - I can't get him shot!
- 快点，艾缀奇！ - 我不能开枪
Thompson!
汤普森！
Anywhere's good,
放哪儿都行
- Is that everything? - Yeah,
- 都在这儿了？ - 是
Yeah?
谁啊？
Come in.
进来
Sergeant James?
詹姆斯上士！
JT Sanborn, man.
我是J.T.桑伯恩
Hey! Hi, how are you? Will.
你好，我叫威尔
Welcome to Bravo Company; welcome to Camp Victory,
欢迎来胜利营B连！
Camp Victory? I thought this was Camp Liberty,
胜利营？我应该在自由营…
Oh! No, they changed that about a week ago.
哦，名字是一周前换的
Victory sounds better.
胜利听上去更顺耳
- All right. Well, at least I'm in the right place, right? - Yeah,
- 好吧，至少我没走错地方 - 没错
While you're here, can you help me move this thing real quick?
既然你来了，能帮我搭把手吗？
Yeah, no problem.
没问题
Maybe you shouldn't take this down.
也许你不该把它扒下来
We get a lot of mortars at night.
晚上常有迫击炮袭击
The plywood on the windows help with the lateral fray coming through.
窗口这些夹板可以挡住侧飞的弹片
That's why it's up there.
所以才装在这儿
Yeah, well, it's not going to stop a mortar round
要是榴弹从天花板飞下来
from coming in through the roof, you know.
这东西就没用了
Besides, I like the sunshine.
而且我喜欢阳光
Hey, I'm sorry to hear about Thompson.
汤姆森的事我听说了，真遗憾
- I know he was a good tech. - Yeah, he was,
- 我知道他拆弹很在行 - 是的
He was a great team leader, too,
他带队也很在行
Yeah, I'm not trying to fill his shoes or anything,
我没想做个完美的接班人
I'm just... I'm just going to do my best.
我只想…只想尽力而为
- Appreciate it, - All right.
- 明白 - 那好
Cool
好得很
Home sweet home, right?
还是自己的窝最好啊
Aren't you glad the Army has all these tanks parked here?
看到我军在这儿停了这么多坦克 你笑得出来么？
Just in case the Russians come we have to have a big tank battle.
就为了提防俄国佬来袭 到时候大家来一场坦克大战
I'd rather be on the side with the tanks, just in case, rather than not have them.
我宁愿备着这些坦克，以防万一 有总比没有好
Yeah, but they don't do anything.
是，但这些家伙根本没用
Anyone comes alongside a Humvee we're dead.
如果有人朝这悍马车跑过来 我们就死定了
Anybody even looks at you funny we're dead,
如果有人奇怪地看着你，我们就死定了
Pretty much the bottom line is if you're in Iraq, you're dead.
差不多可以这么说 如果你来伊拉克，你就死定了
How's a fuckin' tank supposed to stop that?
这鸟坦克能救你的小命么？
- Would you shut up, Owen please? - Sorry
- 欧文，能不能闭嘴？ - 抱歉
Just trying to scare the new guy.
我只是想吓吓新人
I saw a little bit in Afghanistan, too.
在阿富汗的时候我也见识过
- Get your eyes on the road, Eldridge. - Copy that
- 到外面看看路况，艾缀奇 - 收到
Yalla!
让开！
Blaster One, this is Victory Main.
拆弹一号，我是胜利总部
Have you reached your 10-20, yet? Over.
是否抵达座标10-20？完毕
Where the hell are the guys who called this in?
那些叫我们来的家伙都去哪儿了？
Victory Main, Victory Main, this is Blaster Mike.
胜利总部，我是拆弹迈克
Interrogative, do you have an update on position? Over.
地点似乎不对，是否有更新信息？完毕
Victory Main, figures to follow, Three-four-five-three is your grid.
我是胜利总部，座标位于3、4、5、3
Well, that's exactly where the hell I am and I don't see anybody in fatigues,
我现在就站在这鬼地方 但不见任何需援助人员
Give us a second to confirm.
稍等，正在确定坐标
Watch your feet!
留神脚下
Set visual is three-four five-three,
查看座标…3…4…5…3…完毕
Got the Humvee
看到悍马车了
Friendly!
友军！
Ah, here we go.
啊，在这儿
They abandoned their vehicle.
他们弃车了
We got an empty Humvee over here, James.
詹姆斯，这儿有辆悍马，但里面没人
Yeah, I got it.
嗯，我知道了
Let's move.
我们走
Friendly,
友军
- Morning, boys. - Sir.
- 早上好，小伙子们 - 长官好
Don't tell me the bomb's in here with you guys.
别告诉我炸弹和你们在一起
- Step out and I'll show you what's going on - All right
- 借一步，我告诉你发生了什么 - 好
Down on that block 20 meters.
那个街区往前20米
This side of the mosque. east side of the street.
在清真寺这边，路的东边
our informant says he saw a pair of wires
我们的线人说他看到一堆引线
going into a rubble pile
线头埋在一个碎石堆里
- It's a possible IED. - Yeah
- 很可能是土制炸弹 - 恩
- I trust this guy. I know him. - Okay,
- 那个线人我了解，我相信他的判断 - 好的
- I'll handle it, - Do you want to talk him or... - No,
- 我来处理 - 你需要和他谈谈吗？
Good, Keep your boys back, We'll be good, Thank you,
不用了，带着你的兄弟靠后站 由我们来处理，谢谢
Specialist, bring up the Humvee,
技术兵，把悍马车开过来
What's going on?
怎么了？
I'm going to break out the suit.
我要穿上拆弹服
- What about the bot? - I'll take care of it.
- 那机器人呢？ - 我来就好了
Don't you want to send the bot down there to see what it looks like?
不想让机器人先去看看情况？
I'll handle it.
我去搞定就行
That's kind of tight down here, James.
詹姆斯，那儿的情况似乎不妙啊
Ready?
准备好了？
Good?
没问题吧？
You don't have to go down there, We already have the bot halfway up.
你没必要自己去，有机器人可以代劳
I'll be all right.
没事
First day, figure you want to take it easy, right?
今天第一天，你想来个轻松的，对不对？
How's it looking, Eldridge?
怎么样了，艾缀奇？
- Good to go - Let's do it
- 可以出发了 - 开始吧
- Got tools? - Got tools
- 工具在里面？ - 在里面
All right. Let's rock and roll, man.
好吧，我们上路
- He's a rowdy boy - He's reckless
真是个急躁的小子
Blaster One, what's going on?
拆弹1号，发生了什么事情？
Blaster One! What are you doing?
拆弹1号！你在搞什么？
Blaster One, this is Blaster Mike
拆弹1号，这里是拆弹迈克
What's with the smoke on the side of the road?
这路上的烟是怎么回事，完毕
Hey, James, can you hear me?
嘿詹姆斯，能听见吗？
Creating a diversion
我在声东击西
From what? Is there a threat?
对谁？你发现威胁了？
Eldridge, get up on the wall, Move!
艾缀奇，上墙，快点！
Tell me what you see, specialist
看到什么了，技术兵？
All right, I got him
哦，我看到他了
He's walking down range.
他正走出射程
James, the smoke is killing my visibility.
詹姆斯，烟雾完全阻挡了视线
Where are you in relationship to the IED? Are you within 100 meters yet?
你和那炸弹差多远？到没到100米？
Hell, I don't know, but I'll tell you when I'm standing over it, cowboy.
我怎么知道 如果踩到了炸弹，我会告诉你的
Take cover!
注意掩护！
Oh, no, A car stopped in front of him, Sanborn.
哦，不，有辆车停在他面前，桑伯恩！
Shit, James! James, come back now.
该死，詹姆斯！詹姆斯，快回来，快
EOD pulled a nine on this Haji in a car.
排爆小组的人拿着9毫米手枪 对着车里的伊斯兰佬
Want me to send backup?
要派增援吗？
I got it.
我对付就行了
- Sanchez, Hayes! - Negative! Negative!
- 桑切斯，海耶斯！ - 不要，不要
Stand down
留在原地
The blast will come up the block
爆炸会波及大片街区
Stay clear around the corner
呆在街角别动
EOD has the situation under control, over
这儿由排爆小组负责，完毕
- Where you going? - Hold your fire on my command!
- 你要上哪儿去？ - 没有我命令，不许开枪！
Want to back up?
想倒车吗？
Get out of the car!
下车！
What the fuck are you doing?
你他妈想干嘛？
Back up!
往后退！
Hello?
喂？
Want to get back?
想退回去么？
It's that way.
往那边走
Back
回去
Taxi's moving.
计程车开了
Get out of the car! Stop!
停车，从上面下来！
Stay down!
趴好不许动！
Well, if he wasn't an insurgent, he sure the hell is now.
如果他以前不是叛乱分子 那现在总该算了吧
Roger that! That's real funny.
收到，你的话真有趣…
Got something
我发现了些东西
Oh, baby!
嘿，小亲亲
Gotcha
找到了
All right
好了
We're done
完事了
Good to go
可以引爆了，可以引爆了
Come down, specialist.
下来，技术兵
Roger
收到
Got a wire
又发现一根线
Hang on
等等
Where are you going?
你这是要去哪儿啊？
Secondary
还有其他的
Shit
妈的
Take cover! Get in the wall! Get in the wall!
找掩护，躲到墙后面去！
That wasn't so bad. First time working together. What do you think?
初次合作还不错，你觉得呢？
I think us working together means I talk to you and you talk to me
我有情况告诉你，你有情况告诉我 这才叫合作
- We going on a date, Sanborn? - No
- 我们是在约会吗，桑伯恩？ - 不
We're going on a mission.
我们是在完成任务
and my job is to keep you safe so we can keep going on missions.
我负责保护你的安全 这样我们才好继续执行其他任务
It's combat, buddy.
这是战斗，伙计
Hey,
嘿
It's just 39 days.
只剩39天了
Thirty-eight if we survive today.
如果今天不死的话，还剩38天
Hey, it's ''Mr., Be All You Can Be''!
是你啊，“尽我所能”先生
What's up, doc?
有甚么新闻吗，医生？
Not much, How are you?
没什么，你怎么样？
I'm good.
我很好
Got a question about that song, ''Be All You Can Be''.
有个问题,关于那首歌“尽我所能”
What if all I can be is dead on the side of an Iraqi road?
如果尽我所能的结果是横尸伊拉克街头 那我怎么办？
I mean, I think it's logical.
这事不是没有可能
This is war, people die all the time. Why not me?
这是战争，每天都有人死 当然可能也会落到我头上
You got to change the record in our head.
你必须换一种想法
You gotta start thinking about other things.
你得去想些其他的东西
Okay, Stop obsessing... Right now.
别老想这个了
What are you thinking about?
现在你在想什么？
You want to know what I'm thinking about, doc?  - Yeah
- 我在想什么，你想知道嘛？ - 是的
This is what I'm thinking about, doc.
我在想的就是这个
Yo, what's up, my nigger? What's up, man? You cool?
嘿，最近如何，你好吗？
Come on, You want the cool shit? Come on, come on, It's the tight shit, man,
想要好货么？看看嘛，这货很正的
Wanna buy DVD?
要买DVD吗？要买DVD吗？
Fuck you, Come, come, please, please1
去你的…别这样，拜托！
New releases, look.
是新片！
Hello, Hello! Want to buy DVDs? Very good, Very good,
你好你好，要DVD吗？绝赞绝赞的！
How much?
多少钱？
One for five and two for nine,
5元一张，9元两张
Three for twelve.
三张12元怎么样？
Three for thirteen and I don't give you tax. Very good, man. Look.
三张13元，还不加税 东西非常好，你看看
- Look... - No tax?
- 看这儿… - 不加税？
All right, What do you got? What do you got,
好吧，你有些什么片子？
You know, you smart shit, You not like those stupid fuck face.
算你丫聪明，不像那些蠢大粪
Yeah, I'm the smart guy.
是啊，我是聪明人
You're a smart kid, Give me your best one, okay?
你是个聪明的孩子 把你的顶级货给我吧
- Here, this the best one. - This is a good one?
- 给你，这是顶级的 - 这个就是顶级的？
- Yeah, The best shit, man. - Okay
- 绝对顶级，老兄 - 好吧
Here you go, I'll take one.
钱给你，我买一张
- Keep the change - Thank you
- 不用找了 - 谢谢
Want a cigarette?
要香烟吗？
Get out of here, You shouldn't smoke.
才不给呢，你不该抽烟
Thank you. Take it easy.
谢谢，跟你开个玩笑
I need to talk to you about something before we go out again.
在下次任务之前，我得和你谈谈
What's that?
要说什么？
- Yesterday - Mm-hmm
- 昨天的事 - 恩
Wasn't cool
可不好玩
Yeah, I know. You'll get it, though.
我知道，但你会习惯的，会习惯的
- So, you're a ranger, huh? - Yeah,
- 这么说你是个独行侠？ - 对喽
I was in intelligence seven years before I joined EOD,
来拆弹组之前，我在情报部门干了7年
We ran missions in every shithole that you could possibly imagine.
我们在各种恶劣情况下执行任务 对此你肯定有概念
So, I'm pretty sure I can figure out a redneck piece of trailer trash like you.
像你这样居无定所的乡巴佬 我想我是看得蛮透的
Looks like you're on the right track.
看来你已经开始习惯了
We'll see you out there.
我们在外面等你
Let's go, move!
快走
Shit, Get out of the way. Move!
该死，快让开
Hello
你好
- Where is it? - It's behind the wall
- 东西呢？ - 在墙后面
- All right, - See any wires? Any smoke?
有没有看到电线或者烟雾什么的？
No, I didn't look
不，我没有细看
So, how do you know it's a bomb?
那你怎么知道是炸弹？
The car has been parked illegally
那辆车违法停靠在那里
The suspension is sagging. There's definitely something heavy in the trunk,
而且悬挂特别低，后备箱里一定有重物
Right. So, why don't you walk over there and peak inside and tell me what you see.
好，不如你现在过去看看 然后告诉我那里面有什么
You want me to go close to it?
你要我走过去看？
Yeah! No-no, I don't. I'm kidding.
没错…不不，我没那个意思，开玩笑
Shit
妈的！
It's coming from over here!
枪声从那儿来！
Blaster One. You there?
拆弹1号，你在吗？
Blaster One, you hear me?
拆弹1号，听到了吗？
Here
拿着
Shit
见鬼
Let's go, guys.
来啊，伙计们
Let it go.
放手
I got top cover.
我去屋顶掩护！
That's a negative, specialist.
不行，技术兵
Eldridge, you stay with me.
艾缀奇，你得跟着我
Sanborn, you take top covers.
桑伯恩，你去屋顶掩护
Shit
该死
Blaster Mike in position
拆弹迈克，到达指定地点
What do you got?
情况如何？
I got a through and through to the chest, but I got him stable.
子弹贯穿了他的胸膛，但不致命
He's not going to make it.
看来他没希望了
We're leaving in 15 minutes.
如果15分钟内带他离开 那他的伤还有救，长官
Oh, God.
哦，上帝啊
- What's he doing? - I don't know,
- 他在干嘛？ - 我不知道
What are you doing?
你在干嘛？
There's enough bang in there to send us all to Jesus.
那里面的炸药足够大家一起见上帝了
If I'm going to die, I'm going to die comfortable.
如果要死，我也要死的舒服一些
I need my kit and my cans.
把我的家什都拿来
What's going on down there, Eldridge?
怎么了，艾缀奇？
I'm getting his kit and his cans. Cover me, please.
我去帮他拿家什，请给我掩护
Kit and cans
给你
Got a Lot of deck cord, electrical
好多导爆线…是电子起爆
I'm looking for this initiating system
我在找起爆装置
Well, it's not in the back seat.
似乎不在后座里
I don't think.
我不这么想
All right, It's not in the back seat.
好了，它不在后座里
Got a young man on the roof, your 9:00, keep an eye on him.
有个年轻人在屋顶，9点钟方向，盯住了
Roger that
收到
It's not in the front seat.
也不在前座
It's not in the door.
不在门里
Not on the floors.
不在地板上
Not in the glove box.
不在手套箱里
If you haven't found it yet, it's probably under the car.
如果还没找到，有可能在车下面
Yeah, no wire leads under... the car. It's all in here somewhere.
车下面没线，肯定藏在车里
- Hey, Sanborn - Yeah
- 嘿，桑伯恩 - 怎么？
You got eyes on some guy, with a video camera?
你刚才是不是看到一个人 手里拿了摄像机？
No, Where?
没有啊，在哪儿？
He's right at my 12:00, you see him? He's pointing the fucking thing at me
在我12点钟方向，看到了吗？ 他举着那个鸟东西对着我
Shit
该死
Negative, I don't see him.
没有，我没看到他
Hey, Sanborn. He's right at my 12:00, look! 12:00!
桑伯恩，他就在我12点方向
Roger that, I got him.
收到，我看到他了
Getting ready to put me on YouTube.
他想拍下我，然后传到YOUTUBE上
- Little shady,- Yeah, he Looks shady. Keep an eye on him,
- 有点可疑啊 - 我也这样觉得，盯着他。
Okay, So, what's the play?
好，我该怎么做？
Be smart. Make a good decision, over
放聪明点，别胡来，完毕
Got more wire
这里线更多
Leads fucking nowhere
通向什么鬼地方
Fuck!
妈的！
Hey, James, how you doing?
嘿，詹姆斯，你那边怎么样了？
I'm wonderful, How are you?
好极了，你怎么样？
You know, we've been here a while
在这儿呆的时间已经够长的了
We need to get out of here soon.
必须尽快离开这里
Uh-huh,
哦
We got a lot of eyes on us, James. We need to get out of here.
很多人在看着我们，必须快点离开
Roger that, I might figure this out.
收到，我想我能解决
James, we need to get out of here,
詹姆斯，我们必须快点离开
James, do you copy?
詹姆斯，你听到了吗？
Fuck it, I get it.
妈的，我知道了
Fuck me
我靠
- Hey, how's it looking in there, soldier? - All clear
- 嘿，下面情况怎么样？ - 疏散完毕
James, the evac is complete. We can leave.
詹姆斯，人员已疏散完毕，可以撤了
Let the engineers handle this mess,
让工兵来料理后事吧
- We moving? - That's affirmative
- 我们撤么？ - 是的
Interesting
有意思
What's up with James? He's not answering
詹姆斯怎么回事？他没回话
Yeah, I think he removed his headset,
呃，他好像摘掉了耳机
Well, will you tell him to put his radio back on, please?
能不能跟他说，让他戴上耳机？
Hey, James!
嘿，詹姆斯
Sergeant Sanborn is asking if you'll please put your headset back on.
桑伯恩中士问你，能不能戴上耳机
Uh... that's a negative.
呃…他不同意
That, yeah, that's not gonna happen.
- 他不肯戴上耳机 - 该死的
I got eyes on three guys at the Minaret at 6:00.
清真寺尖塔顶上有3个人，6点钟方向
- What the hell is he doing? - I don't know what the fuck he's doing,
他到底在干嘛？
They're communicating with your cameraman.
他们在和摄像的男人联络
This is real bad, man.
不妙啊，老兄
Get behind the Jersey barrier.
蹲到护栏后面去
I can't see James from here.
在这里我看不到詹姆斯
Get down now!
马上给我蹲下！
We can go!
可以走了！
Bastard
王八蛋
We're done.
活干完了
Sanborn, let's get out of here.
桑伯恩，我们走！
That was good.
爽
- Hey, James! - What?
- 嘿，詹姆斯 - 嗯？
Never turn your headset off again.
再也不许摘掉耳机
You the guy in the bomb suit?
你就是那个拆弹员？
No, sir, Sir, that's Sergeant James. He's right here.
不，长官，是詹姆斯上士，他在那里
- Hey, James. - Yeah?
- 嘿，詹姆斯 - 嗯？
Someone's here to see you.
有人找你
You the guy in the flaming car. Sergeant James?
搞定起火轿车的那个就是你？
Afternoon, sir Uh, yes, sir
下午好，是我干的，长官
Well, that's just hot shit.
好，简直太棒了
You're a wild man, you know that?
你是个强人，知道吗？
- Uh, yes, sir - He's a wild man
他是个强人，你们知道吗？
I want to shake your hand.
我想和你握手
- Thank you, sir. - Yeah
谢谢长官
How many bombs have you disarmed?
你拆过多少炸弹？
Uh, I'm not quite sure.
啊，我不是很确定…
- Sergeant? - Yes, sir.
- 上士！ - 是，长官
I asked you a question.
我在问你问题
Eight hundred seventy-three, sir.
873个，长官
Eight hundred! And seventy-three.
八百！七十三！873个！
That's just hot shit.
简直棒到没话说
Counting today, sir, yes. - That's gotta be a record.
今天的也算在里面了，是吗？ 这一定是最高记录
What's the best way to... go about disarming one of these things?
拆这些鬼东西…最好的方法是什么？
The way you don't die, sir.
是活着拆了它，长官
That's a good one.
呵呵，是个好方法
That's spoken like a wild man. That's good.
强人就该这么说话，真不错
- Hey, what's up, man? - Oh, hey, wait a minute,
- 你好啊 - 嘿嘿，等一下
Look who it is.
看看这是谁啊？
I want my five bucks back, buddy.
把5元钱还给我，老弟
Five dollars for what, man? You crazy now?
什么5元钱？你发痴啊？
Yeah, The DVD you sold me was crap.
你卖给我的DVD是什么狗屁东西！
You crazy, man. That's impossible. It's Hollywood special effects.
你胡说，不可能，那是好莱坞特技
- What, you want donkey porn? - It's crap.
- 那你要看什么，兽交？ - 那片子是垃圾
- Girls on dog? - Gay sex, man?
女人和狗做？还是男同志片？
Anything you want, you get.
你要什么，就给你什么
I hook you up, man.
我跟你，那是啥关系
All right, What... what's your name?
哈哈哈哈，好吧，你叫什么名字？
- Beckham. - Beckham like the soccer player?
-贝克汉姆 -贝克汉姆？那个足球运动员？
Yeah, man. It's like soccer player. Now give me my ball.
就是那个足球明星，把球还给我
Are you a soccer player?
你是足球运动员？
Yeah, man, Best of the best. I'm better than Beckham.
是的，我是王中王，比贝克汉姆还强
- You play goalie? - Yes, I play goalie - Okay
- 你会守门么？ - 是的，我会
I'll make you a deal. If you can stop the ball, I'm going to give you five bucks,
那我们来赌一场，如果你能守住我的球 我就再给你5块钱
- but if you can't... - And what if... what if I can't?
- 但如果你没守住… - 没守住怎么样？
Listen to me. If I score, I'm going to keep your ball,
如果我射进你的门，这球就归我
- Deal? - Deal
- 成不成？ - 成
Get up there
过去吧
Go on
走啊
- Let's see what you got hot stuff - Are you ready?
- 看看你有什么能耐 - 准备好了吗？
On three, Ready?
我数到3，你准备好了吗？
One, two, three... Aahh!
1…2…3！啊…
Shit
该死
Come on Where's the five dollars? Man, come on.
快点，我的5块钱呢？
All right, I got ya. Good job, dude.
好吧，我给你，不错嘛，年轻人
Here's five.
五块钱给你
You're an EOD, boomala, boomala.
你是拆弹组的？
That's right.
没错
It's fun, no?
那很有趣吧？
It's cool? It's gangster.
好像黑帮一样，对不对？
Tell you what, I'm going to buy...
那什么，我要买…
Let me see if I have enough money, yeah. Five.
让我看看钱够不够…好，够五块钱
I'm going to buy another DVD, okay?
我要再买张DVD
But if it's shaky... Look at me... or out of focus...
但如果还是晃，或者画面模糊
or any way not 100%,
或者不是百分百的好片
I'm going to chop off your god dammed head with a dull knife.
我就拿把钝刀，把你的小脑瓜子锯下来
How do you feel about that? I'm just kidding.
怕了吧？我只是开玩笑，开玩笑
Here, you're a good kid, man. You're a good kid, aren't ya?
你是个好娃娃，真是个好娃娃
Owen
欧文！
Hi
嗨！
- Hi, sir, - How are you?
- 你好，长官！ - 怎么样？
- I'm good - Good
- 不错 - 很好
- What's wrong? - Brakes are squeaking
- 哪里坏了？ - 刹车的声音不对
Don't trust the mechanics around here. You know.
这里的机修工不太靠得住
- So, how you doing? - Good
- 最近怎么样？ - 我很好
I just want to check the oil.
我去检查下油箱
Yeah, it's good to sleep, eating well...
吃得也好，睡得也香
I'm feeling pretty squared away, actually, doc.
感觉整个人神清气爽，真的
Good to hear it.
听你这么说，我很高兴
So, you getting along with the other soldiers in your unit?
和同部队的战友相处得还好么？
Yeah, My team's great. My team Leader is inspiring.
嗯，我们队很棒，队长很会鼓舞人
- Are you being sarcastic, soldier? - No
- 你是在说反话么？ - 没有
He's going to get me killed.
他正打算送我归西呢
almost died yesterday.
昨天差点就成功了
At least I'll die in the line of duty, proud and strong.
至少是因公殉职，我感到很自豪很光荣
You know, this doesn't have to be a bad time in your life.
这不是你人生的低谷
Going to war is a - is a once in a lifetime experience.
参战是你一生中难得的经历
It could be fun.
也许可以很有趣
And you know this from your extensive work in the field, right?
是丰富的实战经验让你得出这些结论的么？
I've done my field duty.
我已履行了我的兵役
Where's that? Yale?
在哪儿服的役？耶鲁大学？
Look, you don't want me to come around, I won't come around.
如果你不想和我谈，我可以不来找你
These talks are voluntary.
我是出于志愿才来帮你
Look, I'm sorry.
我很抱歉
I appreciate what you're saying, I do.
你能跟我说这些，我很感激，真的
I appreciate our sessions together,
我也很感谢你给我的心理治疗
but you need to come out from behind the wire, see what we do.
但你也需要走到前方去看看 看看我们在做的事情
Well,
好吧
if this circumstance calls for it, I will.
如果情况需要，我会去的
Just like every other soldier.
就像别的士兵一样
Fire in the hole!
目标起爆！
Firing now!
起爆！
- Ready for second det? - Ready
- 准备好第二次爆炸了没？ - 准备好了
Fire in the hole! Fire in the hole, Fire in the hole!
目标起爆！目标起爆！目标起爆！
Whoa, whoa, whoa, Hold on a second!
喂喂喂，等一下
God damn it, I think it forgot my gloves down there.
天杀的，我好像把手套忘在那里了
- What? - I forgot my gloves.
- 什么？ - 我忘拿手套了
Hang on
等一下
You know, these detonators misfire all the time.
这些引爆器很容易误爆啊
What are you doing?
你是甚么意思？
I'm just saying shit happens, they misfire.
我只是说，总免不了有倒霉事 比如可能发生误爆
He'd be obliterated to nothing,
他会被炸成粉粉面面的
His helmet would be left, You could have that.
也许能剩个头盔，那就归你好了
Little specs of hair, charred on the inside.
还有几缕头发，内层或许会有些焦
Yeah, there'd be half a helmet somewhere,
是啊，也许能找到半个头盔
bits of hair.
还有一点点头发
Ask for a change in technique and protocol,
然后我们要求改进技术流程
make sure this type of accident never happen again, you know?
以确保此类事故不再发生
You'd have to write the report.
这样的话，你得写一份报告
- Are you serious? - I can't write it.
- 你是认真的吗？ - 我写不来的
No, I mean, are you serious about killing him?
不，我是问你，真想杀了他？
- Twelve o'clock I see an SUV - Roger that
- 12点钟方向有一辆SUV越野车 - 收到
I got four armed men.
我看到4个全副武装的家伙
They're in Haji gear.
伊斯兰的装扮
All right, go slow and easy.
好，慢慢靠过去
Careful now.
停车
All right, Careful now, guys.
好，各位小心点
- Eldridge, you stay on that 50. - I got 'em.
- 艾缀奇，你守好机枪 - 我把着呢
''Obre... obre...'' put your gun down!
放下枪，放下你们的枪
On your knees! Put your gun down!
跪在地上，放下枪！
- Obre, motherfucker! - Hold up your hands!
- 混蛋 - 把手举高
Get down, motherfucker, Obre!
跪下！ 混蛋
Put your gun down now!
快把枪放到地上！
Put your gun down!
把枪放下！
Advance, advance...
前进，前进
Hands high!
手举高！
- Eldridge, cover! - I got you
- 艾缀奇，掩护！ - 明白
Pistol, off your hip, now!
把背后的手枪扔掉，快点！
What you want me to do?
到底要我干嘛？
Keep my hands up or take off the pistol?
把手举高还是扔掉手枪？
- Keep your hands up - Okay
- 举着你的手 - 好
Easy, easy.
慢点，慢点
Got it!
拿到
Can I touch my fucking head now?
我可以碰自己的脑袋吗？
Slowly
慢一点
We're on the same fucking side, guys.
伙计们，我们是一条战线的
Jesus
哦，上帝
You guys are wired fucking tight, you know that?
你们实在有点草木皆兵了
Well, this is no place for a picnic, right. What are you guys doing here?
这里可不是野餐的地方，你们在这里干嘛？
We have a flat tire, Can you help us?
-我们的车胎爆了，能帮我们吗？
Sure, yeah. You got any spares?
没问题，你们有备胎吗？
We have spares, but we've used up our wrench.
备胎是有，可我们的扳手用光了
How do you use up a wrench?
扳手怎么会用光的？
Well, the uh, the guy over there with the red thing on his head,
呃…那个包着红头巾的男人
he threw it at someone.
他拿扳手当飞镖使了
- All right - Thank you
- 呵，好吧 - 谢谢
That's Chris, this is the wrench man.
这是克里斯，这是扳手男
Hello, wrench man, that's Jimmy.
- 你好，扳手男 - 那个是杰米
You know, you can shoot people here, you don't have to throw a wrench at 'em,
在这里你可以用枪打，不用扔扳手
Fuck off
去你的
Take a look at this,
看看这个
I picked these guys up in Najaf.
这些人是在纳杰夫(伊拉克圣城)抓的
Nine of hearts, that's one,
这个是红心9号通缉犯
And the other... jack of clubs,
另外一个，就是梅花J
- These the same guys? - Yep, That's them.
- 就是他们？ - 没错，就是他们
Does he need a little help there?
他需要帮忙吗？
What's the problem with the tire? Come on.
轮胎到底什么问题？快点！
No good, boss. This wrench is too small.
这个不行，老大，这个太小了
All right, solutions? Anyone?
谁有解决办法吗？
I think there's another wrench in the back of the Humvee if you want to check,
在悍马车后好像还有把扳手
- I'll give it a try. - All right. Let's do it.
- 那我试试看吧 - 好，快点干
How long you guys out here?
你们来这里多久了？
Well, I don't know. Specialist, what do we got?
我不知道，技术兵，我们来多久了？
- We have... 23 more days or 22... - Oh yeah
还有23天吧…不对，还剩22天就…
No one's counting.
没人仔细算过
Contact left!
左边接敌！
Take cover!
找掩护！
Chris, take the 50. Jimmy, take that in the Humvee.
克里斯，上机枪 吉米，拿悍马车里的家伙
- Got it. - Come on!
- 明白 - 快点！
Charlie, go!
查理，走！
Go, go, go!
走！走！
Fucking morons!
混账东西
Get on the side, Charlie Get the Barret and the go-bag, Jimmy.
查理，保护侧翼 杰米，把狙击枪和冲锋包拿来
- What are we shooting at? - I don't know.
- 我们在打谁？ - 我怎么知道
Fuck, the packages are gone!
妈的，通缉犯跑啦！
They won't get far on foot.
他们跑不远的
Bring 'em back those fuckers now. I'm out 500,000 fucking pounds.
把那俩给我逮回来 不能让50万元就这么飞了
it's 500,000 dead or alive.
无论生死，都值50万
- Okay Jimmy, give me the Barret. - Yeah
- 杰米，把巴雷特狙击枪给我 - 好
I can't see a thing.
我什么也看不见
Come on!
来吧！
Chris is shooting wild. Gotta conserve the ammo.
克里斯在乱射…得节约子弹啊
Hey, Chris can you hear me?
克里斯，听到我说话吗？
Hey, Chris! Chris! Can you hear me? Chill out on the 50!
克里斯！听见没？别一个劲开枪！
Roger that.
收到！
- Fifty's down - They shot Chris.
- 机枪哑火了！ - 克里斯被击中了
It must be coming from that building.
子弹一定是从那房子里出来的
I can't see anything.
我什么也看不见
Movement on the roof.
有人在房顶移动
Yeah?
怎么样？
Three meters higher.
再抬高3米
I'm going to adjust.
我调整一下
Fuck
妈的
Fuck, he's dead.
妈的，他死了
We've got to get out of here now!
我们必须马上离开这里
Damm it.
妈的！
This is Alpha Nine. We're in deep shit.
这里是阿尔法9，情况危急
I'll get on the Barret.
我去狙击
Go, go, go!
走，走！
Yeah, we're taking incoming fire.
是，我们受到攻击
- No, Sanborn, don't come up here - Got it!
桑伯恩，别上去
Go, buddy, Stay low! Stay Low!
过去，伙计，压低身体！
I have two KIA,
我方伤亡2人
correction, three KIA... our grid last lock stat...
更正，伤亡3人…现处方位是…
Stay low!
身体压低！
Can you get me some help?
能帮我一下么？
- Behind you - Yeah
- 我来了 - 好
Breathe easy
放松
- I got movement - Yeah
- 发现人影 - 嗯
On the ridge of that house
在房顶上
Eight hundred and fifty meters
距离850米
- See it - By the window
- 看见了 - 在窗边…
- You got target - Got it
- 有个目标 - 看见了
All right, here little left.
有点偏左
Just breathe easy
放松
- I'm out of ammo - Hmm?
没子弹了
I'm out of ammo.
我没子弹了
Eldridge, we need ammo.
艾缀奇，我们需要子弹！
Where is it?
子弹在哪里？
Check on the dead guy, man.
在那死人身上翻翻看
It's on the dead man.
在死人身上
Eldridge!
艾缀奇！
I'm looking.
我在找！
We need that ammo, man.
我们要子弹！
All right, man.
知道了
Oh, here.
好，找到了
Thanks
谢谢
All right. Got it.
好了
Same target.
目标不变
It's fucking jammed.
妈的，卡壳了
Let me see it.
让我看看
Fuck!
妈的
Aw, shit. The blood's making it jam, Eldridge.
该死，血把子弹卡住了…艾缀奇！
Shit!
该死
You gotta clean the blood off, man. It's making 'em jam.
血把子弹卡住了，把血弄干净
Specialist!
技术兵！
- Clean the blood off. - Okay
- 把血擦干净 - 好
Clean it. Clean it.
快点，快点
You gotta clean it, man.
得把它弄干净！
- How? - Spit and rub,
- 怎么弄？ - 吐口水然后擦！
All right
好吧
Spit and rub, buddy. Spit and rub.
吐口水！然后擦！
It's not working, it's not coming off.
好像没用，擦不掉
Spit and rub, Spit and rub. Here, take it out.
给我，先把子弹拿出来
Use your camel, Use your camel. Where is it?
用你的水管夹，用水管夹擦
You all right?
你还好吧？
Here, use that.
就用这个
Just breathe, buddy.
深呼吸
Come on, Just breathe in.
来，放松点
Good. Here, squeeze.
好，拿着，用它擦
- Got it? - Yeah
- 明白了？ - 明白
Rub that olive, baby. Come on, you got it.
擦干净点，小子…嗯，你做的很好
You're doing good, man. You're doing real good.
你做得很好，真的很棒
- Got 'em? - Yeah
- 好了吗？ - 好了
I'm going to keep you safe, buddy, all right?
我会保证你没事的，伙计
Now let's get these bastards, Scan your sectors.
我们去干掉这帮混蛋，守好你的位置
Kill that fuckin' asshole.
杀了那个混账东西
Son of a bitch.
狗娘养的
Nice, he's down. 2nd one out of range.
漂亮！撂倒一个，另一个躲起来了
Twenty meters to the right of the building.
屋右侧20米有一个
I got him.
我看到了
Fire when ready.
瞄准了就打
He's moving, he's moving. To the building.
他跑了，他跑了，往房子方向跑
- Follow him You got him? - Got him
- 跟上他，看见没？ - 看到了
He's down.
他也倒了
Goodnight. Thanks for playing.
晚安，感谢参与
Window, the window. At the window,
窗户，在窗边！
He's still there.
他还在那儿
Left window. Left window, Got him?
左边窗户，左边窗户，看到了吗？
Got him.
看到了
He's down.
打中了
- Hey, Owen? - Yeah?
- 嘿，欧文 - 什么事
Can you grab the juice? out of the pack please?
能不能从包里拿点果汁过来？
Sure
好的
I think we're out.
好像喝完了
- Got anything left to drink? - You could try that one.
- 有什么能喝的吗？ - 试试那个
Thank you.
谢谢你
Drink, drink it.
喝，喝了它
Things are real quiet.
真安静啊
Yeah, I don't like it.
是啊，我可不喜欢
- Hey, Will? - Yeah?
- 嘿，威尔 - 怎么？
At your six o'clock.
在6点钟方向
I see movement on the bridge. Right on the tracks.
我看到桥上有动静！就在小路上
Well, handle it.
搞定他
Should I fire?
我该开枪吗？
It's your call, buddy.
自己决定，伙计
Good job.
干得好
Hey, Sanborn.
嘿，桑伯恩
I think we're done.
我想应该完事了
Okay? You all right?
你没事吧？
That's what you get for hitting your fucking team leader, motherfucker.
狗东西，竟敢打队长，这就是报应
- Man - I'll be right back, I gotta piss.
我马上回来，去撒尿
Owen
欧文！再喝一圈，这是命令！
Well, yes, sir. Sgt, James, sir.
是，长官！
You're not very good with people, are you, sir?
你不太懂相处之道吧，长官
But you're a good warrior, Give me your mug.
但你是名出色的勇士，杯子拿来
There ya go, sir.
喝，长官
You were well on the field of battle today, specialist.
你今天的实战表现非常出色，技术兵
Cheers
干杯
Uh, I'm too old for this shit.
老了，喝不动了
- I was scared. - Yeah?
- 我很害怕 - 是吗？
Well, everyone's a coward about something, you know.
每个人心里都有恐惧
You're good. You're real good.
你是好样的，真是好样的
Just what do we have here?
看看这里有什么？
Will has possessions.
威尔有个小宝箱
I didn't know you owned anything, Will.
我从不知道你有这么多存货啊，威尔
Let's see what you got here, Will.
看看都有些什么
Who is that?
这是谁？
That's my son,
是我儿子
he's a tough little bastard, nothing like me.
他是个难惹的小家伙，不像我
You mean to tell me you married?
你不会是想告诉我，你结婚了吧？
Well, you know, I had a girlfriend and...
我曾经有个女朋友…
...she got pregnant, so we got married.
后来她怀孕了，所以我们结婚了
We got divorced.
后来离了
Or I thought we got divorced.
或者说，我认为我们已经离了
She's still living in the house. And she says we're still together,
她还住在我家，她说我们还是一对
so I don't know, What does that make her?
我就糊涂了，不知道该称呼她什么
Dumb for still being with your ass.
抱着你这种家伙不肯放 不如叫她呆瓜好了
Hey
嘿！
She ain't fuckin' dumb, all right?
她一点也不呆，听见没？
She's just loyal.
她很忠诚
She's just loyal. That's all, How 'bout you guys?
是很忠诚…仅此而已 说说你们的事吧
You got... you got a girl? What do you got?
你…你有女人吗？
My only problem is the girl I do like,
我的问题是，我真正爱的女人
I can't stop her from talking about babies, man.
老是跟我谈孩子，我没辙了
Well, give her your sperm, stud.
那就把你的后代给她啊，种马
Go on. Do it.
去吧，就这么做
- C'mon, chicken. Just give it to her. - No! Hell no!
- 快点，胆小鬼，给她就行了嘛 - 不，绝对不行
Make babies
生孩子去
I know when I'm ready, and I ain't ready for that yet, I know that.
我心里有数，我现在还没准备好
Well, well... what do we have here?
哦…看哪，这是什么？
Uh, components.
呃…是零件
They're bomb parts, signatures.
是炸弹的组件，每个都代表着一个炸弹
Yeah, I see that, but what they doing under your bed?
是，我明白，为什么会在你床下面
Well...
呃
There we go, this one...
看这个
This one is from the UN building.
从一幢联合国大楼拆来的
Flaming car, dead man's switch... Boom,
爆炸车辆，人体起爆
This guy was great, I like him.
这家伙人不错，我喜欢
Ah... Look at this one.
看看这个
This one, y'all, is from our first call together.
这来自我们第一次做的任务
This box is full of stuff that almost killed me.
这盒子里的东西都曾差点要了我的命
And what about this one?
- 这又是什么呢？
- Where's this one from, Will? - It's my wedding ring.
- 这东西从哪儿来的，威尔？ - 这是我的结婚戒指
Like I said, stuff that almost killed me.
我说了，这东西差点杀了我
You know, I just think it's really interesting
我觉得这很有趣
to hold something in your hand that could have killed anyone.
决定许多人生死权的东西 就握在你的手里
Damn that, It's all shit from radio shack.
去你的，都是些从电子市场买来的破烂
It's interesting.
我觉得很有趣
I think it's interesting too.
我也觉得这很有趣
Well, I think you hit me harder than I hit you
另外，我还没对你怎么样呢
therefore I owe you a punch.
你就先对我下重手，不公平
Now get your ass up, C'mon.
快起来，混球！
C'mon, He's right. Let's go, C'mon,
他说的没错，起来
Come on!
来啊
All right, hold on, boys. We need some rules,
好吧伙计们，我先说规则
Sanborn, no face shots.
桑伯恩，不能打脸
Oh, there's gonna be a face shot.
喔，我非得打脸不可
Sergeant James, take off your shirt.
詹姆斯上士，把T恤脱掉
Yes, sir.
是，长官
What happened?
这怎么搞的？
My momma dropped me when I was a baby,
小时候被我妈摔过
Looks like frag scars,
我看像弹片造成的伤疤
- Let it go, Eldridge, C'mon, - All right,
- 让开，艾缀奇 - 好吧
Nice and big
来一记漂亮的重拳
Oohh!
喔~
You like that, huh?
很享受吧？
That's all you got?
你就这点本事？
Come on,
来吧
Bring some, C'mon,
打我，快！
Ooh!
呜噢！
Wooh, God damn!
呜，爽耶！
That's gotta hurt.
够他受的
- You all right, man? - Oh, yeah
- 你没事吧，伙计？ - 没事
- Oh, he's all right. - Get up, bitch.
- 他还行 - 起来，婊子
All right, bitch.
好了，婊子
- What do you got now? - Get the fuck off me?
- 看你还有什么本事？ - 滚开
- What do you got? - Get off me, you mother fucker.
- 还有什么本事？ - 从我身上滚开
What do you got? What do you got?
有什么？什么？
Wooh, he's a wild one. We got a wild one.
他真骚，太骚了
C'mon, Sanborn. Get him. That's right.
来，桑伯恩，对，就这样
- Ride him, baby. - Get off me
- 骑上马儿跑啊 - 从我身上下来，变态
- C'mon, bitch - C'mon, guys
- 动啊，婊子 - 好了，伙计们
What do you got?
有啥能耐啊？
Get off me
滚开
Hey, hey, hey!
好了好了
I'm just kidding, motherfucker, shit!
我跟你开玩笑呢，小畜生
You're all right, Sanborn.
你不简单啊，桑伯恩
You're all right, man.
真的不简单，兄弟
Owen, get this guy a drink. C'mon.
欧文，给他来点酒，去
- You got him? - Yeah, I got him,
- 你扶住他 - 扶住了
- All right, here. - All right.
- 好，我闪了 - 好的
- See you later, - Be safe - All right.
- 回见，当心点
All right, come on big boy. Damn, boy, you need to get on a diet.
好了大块头，我们走…靠，你该减肥了
He hurt his knee,. C'mon, man.
都快站不住了…来
Steps. C'mon.
当心楼梯
Step, step.
一步，两步
All right, lay down. All right, Get some rest.
好了，躺下，好好休息
Hey, James, you think I got what it takes to put on the suit?
詹姆斯，你说我配得上这身军装么？
Hell, no.
你不配
Night, boy.
晚安，小子
- Good morning, Colonel. - Good morning.
- 早上好，上校 - 早上好
Mind if I ride along? I'm sick to death of sitting behind a desk all the time.
能捎上我么？老是干文职，闷死我了
That'd be a privilege. Hop in, Colonel.
- 算是给我的恩惠 - 上车吧，上校
Hey, Doc.
你好，医生
Not to insult your intelligence, sir.
我不是想侮辱你的智商
but if the shit hits the fan, please don't fire out the Humvee.
但如果遇到麻烦，请不要向车外射击
The round will just bounce around, and someone might get shot.
免得搬起石头砸自己的脚 有人会吃枪子的
- I don't like getting shot. - Understood, Sergeant,
- 我可不想吃枪子 - 明白了，上士
Oh, it's a pretty standard mission.
这是个很常规的任务
We're just here to pick up some unexploded ordinance.
我们要去处理一批爆炸军械
Sergeant James is gonna see what the deal is
詹姆斯上士会去现场看情况
and then hopefully we'll be gone in a couple minutes.
希望能在几分钟内搞定
- We've gotta gear up. - For what?
- 我们得带上装备 - 为啥？
Security hasn't gone in.
保安部队没进去过
Go in quiet.
我们潜进去
- Radios off - Roger - Roger that
- 把对讲机关掉 - 明白
- Glad you came. - Stay safe, all right
- 很高兴你能来 - 小心点
Clear
没人
Hey
嘿
cigarette's still smoking.
烟头还在冒烟
It's all our shit.
这些都是我们的了
Mother fucking goldmine.
都堆成一座金山了
Watch out for trips
小心陷阱
I got something
我发现了些东西
I know this kid
我认识这个孩子
His name's Beckham. He sells DVDs,
他叫贝克汉姆，是卖DVD的
You ever see a body bomb before, man?
以前见过人肉炸弹吗？
It's disgusting. Let's get outta here,
太恶心了，我们走吧
Hold it.
等下
Eldridge, want you to grab all the C4 and deck cord you can get your hands on.
艾缀奇，带上所有C4塑胶炸药 引爆线能拿多少就拿多少
Let's get all this ordnance outta here.
把这里的弹药都带走
And we're just gonna... we're gonna blow the place.
然后我们…我们把这儿炸了
Roger, Just blow it.
明白，就炸了吧
What are you doing?
你们在干嘛？
Yeah? Putting the stones in to move.
把这些石头搬上车运走？
Yeah, that's really wonderful
很好
but it's a little bit unsafe today,
但今天有些危险
Yeah, it's a little unsafe.
是的，有些危险
So maybe... I don't know.
也许…
I'm thinking maybe we should move?
…也许我们应该离开？
No?
不行么？
Fuck
妈的！
- You all right? - Yeah
- 你没事吧？ - 是的
- You?
- 你呢？ - 嗯
- You all right, man? - Yeah
- 没事吧？
No one in or out, okay?
周围没人了吧
Cancel the det, Cancel the det.
取消引爆，取消引爆
- What the fuck is he doing? - I don't know, man.
- 他在干嘛？ - 我不知道
I don't know.
我不知道
I'm coming out.
我出来了
Roger that.
收到
- Where are you from? - New York.
- 你从哪里来？ - 纽约
The Big Apple.
就是“大苹果”(纽约昵称)
I'm from Iraq
我是伊拉克来的
I love it here. This is a beautiful place.
我喜欢这里，这里很漂亮
But it's not too safe here, okay?
但是这里不太安全
So, I think we need - we need to move, please.
所以我认为我们应该离开
You think it's that little Beckham?
那个是营地旁的小孩么？
No, I don't.
不，我不这么想
- You're positive? - Sure.
- 你肯定么？ - 当然肯定
Hey, I don't know, man. They all look the same, right?
我不知道，他们看上去都一样
I don't know.
我不知道
- Will seemed sure. That was weird. - Very weird.
- 威尔似乎很肯定，真是奇怪 - 非常奇怪
Please, just move.
请…离开…
Move, Move.
走，走
Move on. Thank you.
离开…多谢
I'm sorry.
很抱歉
Will's very weird.
威尔这人很怪
I mean he keeps bomb parts under his bed.
把炸弹零件收在床下面
I'll bet you he won't keep any of these parts under his bed.
我打赌，今天的炸弹零件 他可不会收在床下面
Bye-bye
再见
Yeah, bye-bye. Bye, thank you.
再见，谢谢
Hey, Colonel
喂，上校
Let's go
我们走
So long, thank you.
再见，谢谢
IED!
土制炸弹！
Cambridge!
坎布里奇！
Get back, get down
回来，趴下
Stay back
呆在后面
Stay back, Sanborn, keep 'em back
呆在后面，桑伯恩！让他们呆着别动
Is anyone hurt?
有人受伤吗？
Cambridge! Fuck!
坎布里奇！妈的
Where's Cambridge!
坎布里奇在哪儿？
Cambridge, come out, We gotta go.
坎布里奇快点，我们要走了！
Oh, he's dead.
上帝啊，他死了
Hey, we gotta find Cambridge, Doc!
得找到坎布里奇！医生！
- Eldridge! - Doc!
- 艾缀奇 - 医生！
Eldridge, c'mon, man, C'mon
艾缀奇，来，过来
I just saw him. He was walking right here.
刚才还看见他，从那边走过来…
I know. He's dead. Look, he's dead, Okay?
我知道，他已经死了，听着，他死了！
It's all right, man.
没事了，伙计
It'll be all right, man,.
会好的，伙计
Hello?
喂…
Will?
威尔？
Hey, let me ask you a question,
我有个问题问你
What happened to the little kid? that used to work here?
原来在这里工作的孩子去哪里了？
Sorry, man, English I... no English.
对不起，我不会说英语
No-no English, You no speak English now.
你不会说英语？
Little kid, Beckham is his name. He sells... sells DVDs,
那孩子叫贝克汉姆，卖DVD的
DVD, One DVD, $5,
买DVD？1张DVD五元
Oh, Jesus Christ.
上帝啊
- $5, - Excuse me, soldier.
- 五元钱 - 打扰一下
you in charge of this area here?
士兵，你是管这里的？
- What's up? - You know this guy?
- 怎么了？ - 你认识这个人？
How do we know that he's not giving intel to insurgents
如果这个人给叛乱分子提供情报
, telling them where to drop mortars?
告诉他们迫击炮往哪儿打，怎么办？
I think he's just selling DVDs.
他只是个卖DVD的
Well, he's a security risk, We should get rid of him.
这关乎安全问题，该把他赶走
What are you looking at?
看什么看？
- He's just selling DVDs, man. All the merchants are clear. - By who?
他只是个卖DVD的 这里所有商贩都是清白的
I couldn't do anything with him without the say-so from my CO.
没有上司命令，我不能对他采取任何行动
Okay, Fuck
好吧，妈的
Fuck
妈的
Does this change anything?
是不是不一样了？
You speak English now. Don't you?
现在你会说英语了，是不是？
- Yalla, yalla, drive! - Okay
- 开车！ - 好的
- OK - Is this his house?
- 到了 - 是这栋房子？
Beckham's house?
贝克汉姆的家？
Wait here
在这等着
Fuck
妈的
Psst, psst, shh.
嘘…
You speak English?
你说英语吗？
English, French, Arabic.
英语，法语，阿拉伯语我都会
Good, Open you vest.
好，背心掀开
Ah, stay there. Stay.
呆在那儿，停
Tell me what you know about Beckham.
把贝克汉姆的事情告诉我
For whom?
谁？
Beckham, 12-year-old boy, body bomb. Stay right there
贝克汉姆，12岁的男孩，人肉炸弹 呆着那儿别动
- I don't know - You don't know
- 我不知道 - 你不知道？
But please, sit down. I am Professor Navid,
请先坐下，我是内韦德教授
This is my home.
这是我家
You are a guest. Please, sit down.
你来了就是客人，请坐吧
I'm a guest?
我是客人？
Just... I'm looking for the people responsible
…我在找相关的人
for-for-for Beckham,
认识贝克汉姆的
You are CIA, no?
你是中情局的？
I am very pleased to see CIA in my home.
有中情局的人来我家，我很高兴
Please, sit.
请坐吧
How can I...
怎么才能…
Be careful, the gun can go off.
当心，枪会走火！
USA friendly coming in.
我是美国军人
Stop! Stop! Get the fuck down!
站住！跪下！
USA friendly,.
我是美国人！
On your knees, Get on your knees now.
跪下！快跪下
On your knees. You will be shot. Don't move.
跪下！否则就开枪了，不许动！
On your knees. Down now.
跪下！快
- Open your jacket! - Opening my jacket,
- 掀开外套！ - 我掀了
Cover. Get him down,
把他摁在地上
- On the ground, - I have a weapon
- 跪下 - 我有武器
Don't fucking move
不许动！
- Tower, hold cover. Searching. - I have a weapon.
- 塔楼，掩护我，我来搜他 - 我有武器
- Gun. - Like I said,.
- 有枪！ - 我早说过了
Weapons clear.
武器已收缴！
ID
身份证
What the fuck are you doing?
你他妈去干嘛了？
I was at a whorehouse.
我去嫖妓了
All right, If I let you in, will you tell me where it is exactly?
好，我让你进去，你告诉我妓院在哪里
Yeah
好…
James, do you copy?
詹姆斯，你听到了吗？
James, do you have your ears on?
詹姆斯，你在听嘛？
James?
詹姆斯？
This is James, What's up?
是我，怎么了？
- Hey - What's up, man?
- 嘿 - 怎么了，伙计？
Look, we have a tank explosion in the Green Zone.
有个油罐在巴格达“绿区”爆炸了 （由美军重点控制的安全区）
We have to post-blast assessment,
要我们去做爆后评估
see if it was a suicide bomber,
看看是不是自杀性爆炸
and if so, how the fuck did he do it?
如果是，再调查一下爆炸手法
Okay.
好
Where'd you say you were again?
你说你刚才去哪里了？
I didn't, sergeant. Let's go.
我没说过…我们走
What happened to your head, James?
你的头怎么了，詹姆斯？
Hey, you ready?
你准备好了吗？
Game face, buddy. Let's go.
把护盔给我，老弟，要上路了
- You ready? - Let's do this.
- 准备好了吗？ - 好了
Rock and roll. Moving out.
好，我们上路了
USA friendlies coming through.
我们是美国友军！
Make room, guys. Make room.
让一让，让一让！
Hey, Sanborn.
喂，桑伯恩
Get a medic! Get a medic!
叫医生来！叫医生来！
- An oil tanker? - Yep,
- 是个油罐？ - 是的
That's a pretty long flight, huh?
- 飞了好长一段路啊 - 是啊
This is the edge of the blast radius.
爆炸一直蔓延到这里
Jesus.
上帝啊
So, where's our triggerman?
袭击者呢？
Burnt up in the flames, man.
已经烧没了
Suicide bomber.
自杀式人肉炸弹
We're never going to find a body in that shit.
根本别想找到半点尸骨
What if there was no body?
如果不是肉体引爆
What if it was a remote det?
而是遥控引爆呢
A really good bad guy hides out in the dark, right?
有个大坏蛋就藏在暗处
Right here. Perfect vantage point,
就在那儿，地势绝佳
outside the blast radius to sit back and watch us clean up their mess.
隔岸观火，看着我们收拾残局
- Want to go out there? - Yes, I do
- 想过去吗？ - 正想如此
You got three infantry platoons behind you whose job it is to go Haji huntin'.
我们连有3个步兵排 他们的职责就是猎杀伊斯兰佬
That ain't our fuckin' job.
这活不该我们干！
You don't say no to me, Sanborn. I say no to you.
你没权驳我，桑伯恩，而我有权驳你
You know there are guys watching us right now.
你知道，那里有群人正在看着我们
They're laughing at this, Okay, I'm not okay with that.
他们正在乐呢…对此我觉得很不爽
Now, turn off your god dammed torch 'cause we're going.
关了你的破手电筒，我们要过去了
Now we know where their oil tanker came from.
现在知道那油罐是从哪儿来的了
No shit. Same kind.
靠，同一型号的
- We're close - Yeah
- 我们快到了 - 没错
The alley ways are probably set up on a grid.
这些小巷应该是纵横交错的
We're going to need to spit up, flush 'em out.
我们必须分路行动，把他们赶出来
Sanborn, you take one, Eldridge, take two,
桑伯恩你走第一条，艾缀奇走第二条
I got three. Rally point at your intersection.
我走第三条，在你的路口集合
- Ready, move - Wait, rally point when?
- 好了，行动 - 等等，什么时候集合？
Fuck
妈的
''Ipsura, ipsura,'' Go, go!
走开，走开！
Shit, Ahh.
该死！
Shit
妈的
- You got contact? - Who was it? What's going on?
- 你遇敌了？ - 是谁？出了什么事？
- What do you got? - It's Eldridge.
- 什么情况？ - 是艾缀奇
Go, go.
走， 走！
Man down! Man down!
人员伤亡，人员伤亡
Shit, Shit, Shit!
该死，该死!
- Negative, negative. It's not him. - He's gone.
- 哦不不，不是他，不是他 - 他离开了
Where'd they go? Where'd they go?
他们去哪儿了？他们去哪儿了？
Tankers and troops are that way.
油罐车和大部队在那边
- Let's go this way. - Fuck
- 我们这边走 - 妈的
Use your torch, On three.
我数到三，你开手电
Ready?
准备好
One, two, three.
1…2…3
- Fuck! - Shit
- 妈的 - 见鬼
Softy, softy, softy.
轻点，轻点，轻点
On three
我数到3
One, Two, Three
1…2…3…
Now! Go, go, go...
快过去！
- Eldridge, you okay? - Fuck, dude, I'm hit.
- 艾缀奇，你还好吗？ - 妈的，我受伤了
Hit him in the fuckin' leg.
他的腿被打伤了
Come on
撑住！撑住！
- Am I dead? Am I dead? - No, You're fine, man.
- 我是不是快死了？ - 不，你没事的，老弟
Am I dead? Am I dead?
我快死了，我快死了
I'm going to put some pressure down. Come on.
我要压住它
You're all right.
你会没事的
Look at me, look at me, You all right.
看着我，看着我！你会没事的
All right, buddy. You ready to get up? On three, ready? One, two, three
好了，我数到3，你站起来 准备好，1…2…3…
Hey, what's up, man? What's up, man?
嘿，你好，伙计
Wanna buy some DVDs? Wanna play some soccer?
排爆男，要买DVD么？ 想踢球么？
What's up?
怎么了？
Come on, man. Wanna play some...
来啊，伙计，来玩…
How you doing, buddy?
你怎么样，老弟？
Doc says you're going to be okay.
医生说你会没事的
My fucking femur is shattered in nine places.
我的大腿骨断成了9段
He said I'll be walking in six months if I'm fucking lucky.
要是在6个月后能走 我他妈就算走运了
- Six months ain't bad, huh? - It's not bad?
- 6个月还好啊 - 还好？
Fuckin' sucks, man,
我靠你老母啊
- Ah, ah! - Take it easy,
喂，轻点
You see that? You fuckin' see that?
看见没？你看见没？
That's what happens when you shoot someone, you motherfucker.
你想请别人吃枪子，结果就成了这样
Sorry
对不起
- Sorry, Owen. - Fuck you, Will.
- 对不起，欧文 - 去你妈的，威尔
Really, Fuck you.
就是这意思，去你妈的！
Thanks for saving my life, but we didn't have to go out.
谢谢你救了我的命 但我们不该去那里找麻烦！
Looking for trouble to get your fucking adrenaline fix, you fuck.
就为了满足你的个人冲动，你个混球！
Hey, take care of yourself, Owen.
好好照顾自己，欧文
Come home safe, man.
祝你平安归来，伙计
- See you on the other side, man. - All right
- 回家再见，伙计 - 好的
Let's get out of this fucking desert!
让我们离开这该死的沙漠！
Don't move
别动！
If you keep walking we will shoot you.
如果你再往前走，我们只好开枪了！
Move him back
让他退回去
Keep that translator back
把那翻译拉回来！
- But the bomb was forced on him. - Get him back!
- 那炸弹不是他自己装在身上的 - 把他拉回来
Don't move! Stay still
站在原地别动！
If you keep walking we will shoot you. If you keep walking we will shoot.
如果你再往前走，我们只好开枪了！
Get that translator back, now!
快把那个翻译拉回来！
Hey, what do you got?
嘿，什么情况？
He came walking up to our checkpoint,
他自己来到我们检查站
said he had a bomb strapped to him, But he's sorry, doesn't want it to go off.
说自己身上绑着炸弹 但他不想让炸弹爆炸
Then he starts begging us to take it off of him.
所以求我们拆除炸弹
Help this man, he's not a bad man.
帮帮他，他不是坏人！
He's not a bad man? He got a bomb strapped to him,
他不是坏人？他绑着炸弹！
This is a joke, he's trying to pull us closer.
他在逗我们，想让我们靠近他
Yeah, I got it, I got it.
好了，我明白了
All right, look... Tell him to open his shirt slowly
好，告诉他，让他慢慢地解开衣服
and see what's inside.
我要看看里面是什么
Slowly, slowly...
慢点，慢点
Jesus
啊，天哪！
All right Sergeant, I need a 75-meter perimeter.
好了中士，让这些人离开75米远
- Get these guys back. - Give me 75 meters. Get back.
- 让他们退后 - 离开75米，往后退！
You tell him to get on his knees and touch the sky, okay?
你告诉他，让他跪下，手举起来
Get down
跪下！
Okay, I need your radio.
好，我要用你的无线电
- Can't we just shoot him? - No
- 能不能射杀了他？ - 不行
He's a family man. He's not a bad man.
他是个有家室的人，不是坏人
He's asking for help, only help.
他只想求助，求我们帮忙
Yeah, all right. You don't want to die, get back! I got it.
好了，如果你不想死，就退到后面去！ 我已经知道了
Listen, I know we've had our differences.
听着，我知道我们有分歧
It happened, all right. It's water under the bridge.
这种事情总难免，但都已经过去了
This is suicide, man.
但你现在是去自杀，伙计
That's why they call it a suicide bomb, right?
所以才称为自杀炸弹嘛
Let's do this. Come on.
我们来搞定它吧
He says the bomb may have a timer, please hurry.
他说炸弹上可能设置了定时器 请快点！
- We're good, Ready? - Yep
- 我好了，你好了吗？ - 好了
Go get 'em
去吧
- Let's do it - See you
- 开始了 - 回见
Get your hands up
举起手！
He says he has a family
他说他有家庭
Please help him,
请帮帮他
Now, listen
听好了
Look, It'd be a lot easier for me to disarm this
如果我要拆炸弹，比较简单的方法是
if I just shoot you. Do you understand?
…先把你杀了，你明白吗？
What's he saying?
他说什么？
He says I don't wish to die, I have a family... Please take this off me.
他说他不想死，他还有家 请你把这东西从他身上拿下来
Tell him to put his hands behind his head or I'll be very happy to shoot him.
告诉他，把手放在头后面 否则我很想开枪打他
Look, that's not what I said.
我不是这么说的
Tell him to put his hands behind his head or I will shoot him.
告诉他，把手放在头后面 否则就毙了他
Listen
听着
Listen, listen.
听着，听着
You understand?
你听明白了？
Okay
好
What do you got here?
看看有什么？
He has four children.
他有四个孩子
Shit
见鬼
Sanborn, we got a timer, and we got a lot of wires, man.
桑伯恩，这有个计时器，还有很多线
I'm going to need a little help on this.
我需要帮助
Roger that, tell me what you need.
收到，告诉我，你要什么？
Bolt cutters
我要钳子
You gotta get down here in two minutes or we're all fucked.
最好在2分钟内给我，不然就完了
Roger that, I'll be there in 30 seconds.
收到，30秒内给你
He says, please, I have a family.
他说求求你  我有个家庭
I know, it's okay. You're all right. You're all right,.
我知道，没事的，你会好的，会好的
Please, don't leave me.
别离开我
You weren't fuckin' kidding.
你没在开玩笑吧
Nope, What's this made out of?
没有…这是什么做的？
Oh, man
老天
This case's harder than steel
这玩意儿和钢一样硬
Shit
该死
- What's our time? - We got two minutes - Shit
- 还有多久？ - 还有2分钟
We're going need a torch to get this off.
得用焊枪才行
Well, we don't have one of those in the fucking truck, man.
我们车里可没那玩意儿
He's dead, man.
他死定了，伙计
Hold on, man. Let me think. Just Let me think.
慢着，让我想想，让我想想
We're going to handle this. It's okay. We got this,
我们会搞定的，没问题，想想…
Shh, okay.
嘘，别吵
Now listen, you're gonna get back.
听着，你先退开
It's just we don't got enough time, Sanborn.
我们时间不够了，桑伯恩
I just gotta... I gotta get these bolts off.
我打算…我打算把这些锁拧断
No, We got a minute and a half, man. We gotta get out of here.
不，我们还有1分半钟，必须离开这儿
- I'll handle this. Just go. - Come on, man.
- 这里我来处理，你快走 - 少来了，伙计
Look, I'm right behind ya. Just go.
我马上就来，你先走吧
Fuck him! Come on, Let's go,
去他的，我们快走！
- Sanborn, I got the suit. Just go, - James!
- 桑伯恩！我有防护衣，你快走！ - 詹姆斯！
Sanborn, you have 45 seconds. You have 45 seconds. Sanborn, Leave,
桑伯恩，还有45秒 你有45秒钟，离开！
You're fucking dead, man. Dead.
你死定了，死定了
Go!
走！
- Everybody get back! - Go, go!
- 所有人往后退！ - 走，走！
We got one.
拆掉了一个
Go, get back.
走，退后！
I can't. There's too many locks. There's too many, I can't do it,
不行，锁太多了，太多了，我干不了
I can't get it off. I'm sorry, Okay!
我没法全弄掉，对不起了
You understand? I'm sorry,
明白嘛？我很抱歉，
I'm sorry. You hear me? I'm sorry,
对不起，对不起
- Get down now! - I can help him.
- 快趴下 - 我去帮他
Everybody stay down!
大家趴下！
James!
詹姆斯！
Everybody up and out,
大家都起来，詹姆斯！
You all right?
你还好吧？
Aw, man,
哦，伙计
I fuckin' hate this place.
我真他妈讨厌这鬼地方
Here, man. Have a hit.
给你，喝一口
I'm not ready to die, James.
我还没准备死呢，詹姆斯
Well, you're not going to die out here, bro.
你不会死在这里的，兄弟
Another two inches.
就差2英寸
Shrapnel zings by, slices my throat.
弹片呼啸而过，然后把我的喉咙割破
I bleed out like a pig in the sand,
我会像头猪一样，在沙漠里流血不止
Nobody'll give a shit.
没有人会在乎我
I mean, my parents'll care, but they don't count, man, Who else?
我父母当然会在意，但他们不能算 老兄，还会有谁在意呢？
I don't even have a son.
我连儿子都没有
Well, you're going to have plenty of time for that, amigo.
想生儿子，你有的是时间，朋友
- Naw, man - You know?
- 不，伙计 - 这你知道
I'm done,
我不想干了
I want a son,
我想要个儿子
I want a little boy, Will.
我想要个小男孩，威尔
I mean, how do you do it, you know?
我想知道，你是怎么做的
Take the risk?
去冒那样的风险？
I don't know, I just...
我不知道，我只是…
- I guess I don't think about it.
我只是从来不去想
But you realize every time you suit up,
但是当你每次穿上拆弹服
every time we go out
每次我们出勤
it's life or death. You roll the dice
就会面对死亡 你赌上自己的命
and you deal with it.
去处理这些事情
You recognize that, don't you?
这些你都清楚，是不是？
Yeah
是的
Yeah, I do.
是这样没错
But I don't know why.
但我不知道为什么
Yeah.
对
I don't know, JT. You know why I am the way I am?
我不知道…知道我为什么会这样？
Naw, I don't.
我不知道
- Wow! You did some shopping. - Yeah.
- 哇，你买了不少东西！ - 是啊
I got some soda. We done?
我买了些苏打水，可以去结账了么？
You want to go get us some cereal and I'll meet you at the checkout?
帮我们拿些麦片来，在收银台会合？
Okay, cereal.
好吧，麦片
Where?
在哪儿…？
Some guy drove his truck to the middle of an Iraqi market,
有人把货车开到伊拉克一个集市中央
starts passing out free candies.
开始发放免费糖果
All the kids coming running up, the families stuff,
所有孩子都跑过去，还有孩子的家人
He detonates.
那人引爆了炸弹
They're saying 59 are dead.
据报道有59人死亡
You know they need more bomb techs.
他们需要补充拆弹员，这你知道
You want to chop those up for me?
帮我把这些切碎
Yeah
对了
You love playing with that.
你喜欢玩这个啊
You love playing with all your stuffed animals.
你喜欢玩毛绒玩具
You love your mommy, your daddy, your nature pajamas.
你喜欢妈妈，喜欢爸爸 喜欢你的小睡衣
You love everything, don't you? Yeah
你什么都喜欢，是不是？
You know what, buddy?
知道吗？
Once you get older,
等你长大了
some of the things that you love might not seem so special anymore.
曾经喜欢的东西也许会变得不再特别
Like your Jack In The Box,
就像这个玩偶盒
Maybe you realize it's just a piece of tin and a stuffed animal
你会发现那只是一片铁皮加一个人偶
and then you forget the few things you really love,
那些原本钟爱的东西会渐渐被你遗忘
And by the time you get to my age maybe it's only one or two things,
到了我这个年纪，钟爱的东西 也许只剩下一两件了
With me I think it's one,
对我来说只剩一件了
- Welcome to Delta Company - Sergeant
- 欢迎来到D连 - 中士